El padrino: The Latin Godfather is a action, crime,
drama film directed by Damian Chapa.
In the streets of East Los Angeles, Manny is a formidable drug dealer.
Impressed by his extravagant lifestyle and prowess, his young
son, Kilo, yearns to follow in his footsteps.
Kilo resolves to learn how to prosper in the drug
world, and his new life as a dealer begins.
In a world where a man wants everything, he may end up with nothing.
Kilo, played by Damian Chapa.
Loco, played by Sal Lopez.
Rudy, played by Emilio Rivera.
Sebeva, played by Jennifer Tilly.
Atty. Gen. Navarro, played by Faye Dunaway.
Jessica Lancaster, played by Joanna Pacula.
El Padrino is a 2004 American film directed by Damian Chapa.
The film stars Chapa himself, depicting his life from a child, to his
becoming the head of a notorious American narcotics syndicate.
Co-starring in the film are: Jennifer Tilly, Faye Dunaway, Kathleen Quinlan, Robert Wagner,
Tommy 'Tiny' Lister, Gary Busey, Joanna Pacula, Rachel Hunter, and Stacy Keach.
Written and produced by Troy Barker, Damian Chapa and Carlton Holder.
The film's producers are Warren Barnhart, Berta Bennett, Chuck Binder, Chris
Chanowski, Edmund Druilhet, Roffe Joundour, Alex Pinedo, H.
Evie Ryland, Robert Star, Harry Sutherland and Lloyd White.
The tone is emotional.